{
    "id": "56cd1138d50e48c38ee3613f6faf7b71",
    "title": "Grammar Exercise (Intermediate Level)",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "She worked so …………………… that her health deteriorated.",
            "description": "Hard can be an adjective or adverb. ",
            "answers": [
                "hard",
                "hardly"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "7c4570026eb8433b9a9e0ee811146051"
        },
        {
            "question": "Hoping to hear from you ………………………..",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "early",
                "soon",
                "soonly"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "3009299a7309454d980b1cacf6bc3b1e"
        },
        {
            "question": "He narrated the whole incident in …………………………",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "detail",
                "details"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "4426c9ae53ba49b9b29bc073347665e1"
        },
        {
            "question": "She is ……………………… charming.",
            "description": "Too has a negative meaning. It is used to talk about unpleasant extremes. ",
            "answers": [
                "so",
                "too",
                "very"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "8147bbd50a6c43948c821be60855773d"
        },
        {
            "question": "She has a ……………………….. smile.",
            "description": "Lovely is an adjective.",
            "answers": [
                "love",
                "lovely",
                "lovingly"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "049ce03a66de404087abebfb31c40119"
        },
        {
            "question": "I feel …………………….. for her.",
            "description": "You feel bad for a person. You need something badly. ",
            "answers": [
                "bad",
                "badly"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "e1088ea6632b477c895e4a6a22692db7"
        },
        {
            "question": "She drove ………………………..",
            "description": "Carefully is the adjective modifying the verb drove. ",
            "answers": [
                "careful",
                "carefully"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "d45b0be390784f3fb54bc66288e07def"
        },
        {
            "question": "You have …………………….. eaten anything.",
            "description": "Hardly means scarcely or almost nothing. ",
            "answers": [
                "hardly",
                "hard"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "ba7c064ed40e4fd1a21b24c3f09f0f7d"
        },
        {
            "question": "Get ……………………. soon.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "well",
                "better",
                "good"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "87f003d3a1b542159cf9164318ade761"
        },
        {
            "question": "Is she getting any ………………………?",
            "description": "The comparative form is used when there is an idea of change. ",
            "answers": [
                "good",
                "well",
                "better"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "590ac375a98c4f409eeaa8ed5c8b826a"
        },
        {
            "question": "She looks …………………………",
            "description": "Look is a copular verb we use adjectives to modify copular verbs. ",
            "answers": [
                "beautiful",
                "beautifully"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "baf6baf9e168431884758da06966ffa6"
        },
        {
            "question": "The soup tasted ………………………..",
            "description": "Taste is a copular verb we use adjectives to modify copular verbs.",
            "answers": [
                "awful",
                "awfully"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "0e1e7b363fa64a8cbaafc35987ec8760"
        }
    ]
}